Hey...
It's dangerous here...
Fly away...
...somewhere... far away.
Falco!
--Huh? What's my brother doing here?
--Good!
You're still talking!
Colt!
Time to run! Hold on!
Falco!
Colt? Status report?
It was a direct hit.
The Eldian unit at the front got blown away.
And the trench?
It's hopeless! We can't dig any farther!
We can't? You're calling the shots?
An Eldian, giving orders?
Watch your tone with
Commander Magath, you mutt!
But... at this rate...
Falco, are you drunk?
He must've hit his head good.
Do you remember this war
we've been in for four years?
Who... are you guys?
Wait... Huh?
Wasn't I flying around
with a sword just now?
Like, whoosh!
And there were Titans that I--
Guess I'll just have to explain
everything from the start.
Listen up good, Falco.
This battle is the climax of a war
that's lasted four years.
If we can take out Fort Slava...
Well, technically, if we sink the Mid-East
Allied Forces fleet in its port...
...it'll spell victory for Marley
and end the war.
But unless we take Fort Slava
sitting on the high ground,
it's hopeless to attack the port.
Why can't the Marley fleet just do it?
Seriously, Zofia?!
You have faith in the fleet?!
--It took those imbeciles four
years to control the seas!
--Ow! Ow, Ow! Ugh! Ow!
--It took those imbeciles four
years to control the seas!
--Ow! Ow, Ow! Ugh! Ow!
--And guess what?! They lost
half their damn ships doing it!
Now they're telling us they're too
chicken to attack till we take the fort?!
Screw 'em all! They're pricks!
Udo, you're gonna squeeze Falco's head off.
Whoops! Sorry!
So what's the deal? Why'd they send us
Warrior candidates to the front lines?
To judge us, obviously.
To pick which one of us
will be the next Warrior.
The time is coming.
Commander Magath chose the
front lines to be our final test.
He knows what's on the horizon.
The plan to conquer Paradis
needs a main player--
the successor of the Armored Titan!
"The Other Side of the Sea"
The Armored Titan...
I wonder which one of us it'll be...
Really, Gabi? Sounds to me like you're
saying none of us come close to you.
Because you don't, right?
Well, Gabi does have us beat.
As far as our grades go.
No. There's more to it than grades, Udo.
I keep telling you.
The difference between us
is that I'm prepared.
To shoulder the fate of us Eldians...
...and to slaughter that island of devils
who've done nothing but make us suffer!
I'm gonna win this battle
and prove that the Eldians left
in this world are good Eldians!
I refuse to lose till I free everyone
from the internment zone!
Um, what exactly are you doing?
Pretty cool, right?
It won't work, Commander Magath!
We can't destroy the railroad without
the machine gun slaughtering us first.
They've got soldiers along
every inch of the trench.
To top it off, the fort can
bombard us whenever they want.
If we stay here too long,
they'll just shower us with shells!
Do you have a better idea, Colt?
We should let Jaw and Cart loose.
Galliard and Pieck will get it done.
They'll wipe out the trench
and bunker in a flash.
No.
If we play our cards wrong, we lose.
Commander Magath, "that" showed up.
What's "that"?
That. An armored train.
It's equipped with four
massive cannons in total.
They're the Allied Forces' new
weapon--anti-Titan cannons.
If one of those 150mm rounds hits
a Titan, it'll kill it in a single hit.
Even one of the Nine.
But both of our Titans are incredibly fast.
The odds of hitting their nape--
And if they did?
We would lose a Titan and a Warrior...
...with no guarantee that
we get their powers back.
That's right. Just like our plan nine
years ago to retake the Founding Titan
resulted in us losing the
Colossal and Female Titan.
The perceived hit to Marley's military
might is what sparked this war,
putting the Paradis Island Operation on hold.
What is it that makes our
motherland Marley so great?
The Power of the Titans.
Correct. Our nation won't last
if we keep losing 'em.
The Power of the Titans is absolute,
and it must always remain that way.
Prepare the Eldian unit for attack!
Yes, sir!
Commander Magath! But that's--
What's the matter, Eldian?
Are you not warriors who
swore loyalty to Marley?
This is a chance for the 800 Eldians here...
...to serve our motherland with honor.
All creatures drink of joy at nature's breast...
Everyone up! Prepare to attack!
C'mon! Stand up!
Eldians!
Your mission is to assault and
destroy the enemy railroad!
The suicide squad will rush the bunker
and disable the machine gun!
Listen up! Let your actions purge the
disgrace of being spawn of the devil!
This is your chance to be honored
by our great motherland Marley!
Prove yourselves worthy!
Yes, sir!
You Warrior candidates are to stand by.
The 800-strong Eldian unit must
destroy the rail at whatever cost.
As long as that armored
train is patrolling the fort,
the Armored and Beast Titan
can't do what they came for.
But...
Colt. As the chosen successor
of the Beast Titan,
learn what it means to lead already.
Perfect. We can destroy the train, too.
Please, let me take a shot at it.
--Huh?
--Ta-da!
If you'll let me, I can disable
the armored train all on my own!
Hey, Gabi!
How much do you think Marley's spent
training you all these years? Hell no.
It's true... I am exceptional
compared to Falco and the others.
There may never be another
Warrior as talented as I am.
Not to mention one this cute.
But if I succeed, we won't lose
the whole unit of 800 Eldians!
And if you fail?
You lose just one promising candidate
and seven hand grenades.
If you think I'm more valuable than 800
Eldian soldiers, I totally understand.
You love me so much that you'd rather sacrifice
the lives of 800 soldiers over me--
Fine.
Go ahead.
Gabi, don't--
I swear! I will prove to you that I'm worthy
of inheriting the Armored Titan!
What are you doing?
For this to succeed...
...please allow me to remove my armband.
Very well.
Hey, someone's coming this way.
It's a woman. Girl, actually.
I think she's surrendering.
No, wait. She might be Eldian.
It looks like something's wrong with her.
She's dragging her leg.
What if she's Eldian?
Shoot her before she turns into a Titan.
Screw that. If you wanna
shoot her, you do it!
Shit.
What the--?
Wait...
Wait for it!
Wait!
She ain't moving.
Who cares? Shoot her!
Now's my chance!
She really did it!
Galliard! Hurry up!
Dammit! You Marleyan cowards!
This is why you bastards...
...all deserve to die!
Gabi!
Falco, don't!
Galliard! Huh?
The armored train has been disabled.
We'll now commence the airborne assault.
Remember to stick to the plan.
Zeke will be our spear...
and Reiner will be our shield.
"Marley: A Military Dictatorship"
"Utilizing seven of the Nine Titans as
'Warriors,' Marley conquers enemy nations
with their overwhelming strength."
Damn, that hurts!
Why'd a Marleyan like me get shot at?!
--What are you doing, Falco?
--You Eldians are supposed
to soak up the bullets!
--Can't you tell?
--You Eldians are supposed
to soak up the bullets!
He's in no shape to fight us anymore.
Udo, gimme a tourniquet.
--Here.
--Stupid kids.
Screw the enemy.
Is that supposed to be your selling point?
You really think obeying the laws of war
will earn you the spot of Armored Titan?
It's not gonna help, you know.
Like I care?
Weirdo.
He's saying something.
Interpret, Udo. Say I stopped his
bleeding and that he'll be fine--
"Don't touch me."
"I'll be tainted."
"You devil," he says.
Retreat!
Hurry up!
Get away from the fort!
Don't get caught in it!
It's begun.
Ahem!
No! Stop!
Truly devils...
Our Marleyan ancestors
were eaten, just like that.
By you Eldians.
Fire!
The kinetic bombardment went well,
but due to the altitude,
roughly half died on impact.
A lot of the anti-Titan cannons
are still operational.
Twenty-eight... Twenty-nine...
And now I know their locations. But still...
More walls?
I'm sick and tired... of walls.
--It's the Armored!
--Kill it!
Fire!
Anti-Titan shells that
penetrate even my armor?
What the--?! What hit me?!
An armored train? There's another?
Shit!
Fire--
Galliard!
You son of a whore!
Nice!
They got it under control?
Our defeat brought about this war, Reiner.
Isn't war a terrible thing?
Finally... With this, the war will be over.
Huh?
What?!
With their fleet destroyed,
the Mid-East Allied Forces signed
a peace treaty with Marley.
The war spanning four years
ended in a Marleyan victory.
But as the world learned that the era
of Titan domination was coming to an end,
Marley was pressed to obtain the
Founding Titan as quickly as possible.
Oh, no...
Thanks to the incredible bravery of the
Marley army, Fort Slava has fallen at last!
Unbelievable!
That's our Marley army for you!
"Titans are not absolute."
Marley was shown this painful reality.
Victory providing a brief joy,
the warriors return to
their hometown of Liberio.